const DATA = {
  decks: {
    "4y3oorycieezyh1ot0i1d": {
      id: "4y3oorycieezyh1ot0i1d",
      name: 'Deck 1',
      cardIds: ['n58opvtvh7i9xccihllhg7', "3umjahn8mj5eikqzqz7au", "a88hjw7cpcp322i6s018ph", "42m9kg2b726w12eak1onl"]
    },
    "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk": {
      id: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      name: 'Deck 2',
      cardIds: [
        "gz32wnwx34rhletpu5faik", 
        "nvqpue6ibecvoueuhtw0xk", 
        "6nuoa2kgk1h40uqaue7z3a", 
        "vd1fj8v4ooiwi3t071lbh", 
        'ebvdc4wysoo5lhy381lln', 
        "bw4hbm1e9kfqxagaeyvpid", 
        "1h2l5i71d5pzro6a97dbwd", 
        "x8cfy94sb3bv79yacn0md", 
        "l5bzzrrxe67k1lycj7zp6", 
        "xndlyrcekqtgvdbbyz6y", 
        "kz5054lofi9xciqwaht69"]
    }
  },
  cards: {
    'n58opvtvh7i9xccihllhg7': {
      id: 'n58opvtvh7i9xccihllhg7',
      deckId: "4y3oorycieezyh1ot0i1d",
      question: 'Deck 1, Question 1',
      answer: 'Deck 1, Answer 1'
    },
    "3umjahn8mj5eikqzqz7au": {
      id: "3umjahn8mj5eikqzqz7au",
      deckId: "4y3oorycieezyh1ot0i1d",
      question: 'Deck 1, Question 2',
      answer: 'Deck 1, Answer 2'
    },
    "a88hjw7cpcp322i6s018ph": {
      id: "a88hjw7cpcp322i6s018ph",
      deckId: "4y3oorycieezyh1ot0i1d",
      question: 'Deck 1, Question 3',
      answer: 'Deck 1, Answer 3'
    },
    "42m9kg2b726w12eak1onl": {
      id: "42m9kg2b726w12eak1onl",
      deckId: "4y3oorycieezyh1ot0i1d",
      question: 'Deck 1, Question 4',
      answer: 'Deck 1, Answer 4'
    },
    "gz32wnwx34rhletpu5faik": {
      id: "gz32wnwx34rhletpu5faik",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 2',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 2'
    },
    "nvqpue6ibecvoueuhtw0xk": {
      id: "nvqpue6ibecvoueuhtw0xk",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 3',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 3'
    },
    "6nuoa2kgk1h40uqaue7z3a": {
      id: "6nuoa2kgk1h40uqaue7z3a",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 4',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 4'
    },
    "vd1fj8v4ooiwi3t071lbh": {
      id: "vd1fj8v4ooiwi3t071lbh",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 5',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 5'
    },
    'ebvdc4wysoo5lhy381lln': {
      id: 'ebvdc4wysoo5lhy381lln',
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 6',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 6'
    },
    "bw4hbm1e9kfqxagaeyvpid": {
      id: "bw4hbm1e9kfqxagaeyvpid",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 7',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 7'
    },
    "1h2l5i71d5pzro6a97dbwd": {
      id: "1h2l5i71d5pzro6a97dbwd",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 8',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 8'
    },
    "x8cfy94sb3bv79yacn0md": {
      id: "x8cfy94sb3bv79yacn0md",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 9',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 9'
    },
    "l5bzzrrxe67k1lycj7zp6": {
      id: "l5bzzrrxe67k1lycj7zp6",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 10',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 10'
    },
    "xndlyrcekqtgvdbbyz6y": {
      id: "xndlyrcekqtgvdbbyz6y",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 11',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 11'
    },
    "kz5054lofi9xciqwaht69": {
      id: "kz5054lofi9xciqwaht69",
      deckId: "giv3ntgzob56wn55z1wgk",
      question: 'Deck 2, Question 12',
      answer: 'Deck 2, Answer 12'
    }
  }
}

export default DATA